campdoc.com 2017-10-26

# Privacy Policy - DocNetwork

This Privacy Policy provides our policies and procedures for collecting, using, and disclosing your information. Users can access a DocNetwork service: CampDoc.com, ChildCareDoc.com, SchoolDoc.com (the “ ** **Service**** “) through our websites app.campdoc.com, app.childcaredoc.com, app.schooldoc.com, applications on Devices, through APIs, and through third-parties. A “ **Device** ” is any computer used to access the DocNetwork Service, including without limitation a desktop, laptop, mobile phone, tablet, or other consumer electronic device. This Privacy Policy governs your access of the DocNetwork Service, regardless of how you access it, and by using our Services you consent to the collection, transfer, processing, storage, disclosure and other uses described in this Privacy Policy. All of the different forms of data, content, and information described below are collectively referred to as “information.”

#### The Information We Collect And Store

**Information You Provide**. When you register an account, we collect some personal information, such as your name, phone number, credit card or other billing information, email address and home and business postal addresses.

**Files**. We collect and store the data and files you upload, download, or access with the DocNetwork Service (“Files”).

**Log Data**. When you use the Service, we automatically record information from your Device, its software, and your activity using the Services. This may include the Device’s Internet Protocol (“IP”) address, browser type, the web page visited before you came to our website, information you search for on our website, locale preferences, identification numbers associated with your Devices, your mobile carrier, date and time stamps associated with transactions, system configuration information, metadata concerning your Files, and other interactions with the Service.

**Cookies**. We also use “cookies” to collect information and improve our Services. A cookie is a small data file that we transfer to your Device. We may use “persistent cookies” to save your registration ID and login password for future logins to the Service. We may use “session ID cookies” to enable certain features of the Service, to better understand how you interact with the Service and to monitor aggregate usage and web traffic routing on the Service. At no time is your personally identifiable information stored within a cookie.

#### How We Use Personal Information

**Personal Information**. In the course of using the Service, we may collect personal information that can be used to contact or identify you (“Personal Information”). Personal Information is or may be used: (i) to provide and improve our Service, (ii) to administer your use of the Service, (iii) to personalize and improve your experience, and (iv) to provide or offer software updates and product announcements.

**Analytics**. We also collect some information to monitor and analyze use of the Service, for the Service’s technical administration, to increase our Service’s functionality and user-friendliness, and to verify users have the authorization needed for the Service to process their requests. As of the date this policy went into effect, we use Google Analytics. You may review the privacy policy of [Google Analytics](http://www.google.com/intl/en/policies/), and opt [out of](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en) this service if you wish.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

**Service Providers, Business Partners and Others**. We may use certain trusted third party companies and individuals to help us provide, analyze, and improve the Service (including but not limited to data storage, maintenance services, database management, web analytics, payment processing, and improvement of the Service’s features). These third parties may have access to your information only for purposes of performing these tasks on our behalf and under obligations similar to those in this Privacy Policy.

**Compliance with Laws and Law Enforcement Requests; Protection of Rights**. We may disclose to parties outside DocNetwork, information and files stored in your DocNetwork and information about you that we collect when we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (a) comply with a law, regulation or compulsory legal request; (b) protect the safety of any person from death or serious bodily injury; (c) prevent fraud or abuse of DocNetwork or its users; or (d) to protect the property rights of DocNetwork.

**Business Transfers**. If we are involved in a merger, acquisition, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your information may be transferred as part of that transaction, but we will notify you (for example, via email and/or a prominent notice on our website) of any change in control or use of your Personal Information or Files, or if either become subject to a different Privacy Policy. We will also notify you of choices you may have regarding the information.

**Non-private or Non-Personal Information**. We may disclose your non-private, aggregated, or otherwise non-personal information, such as usage statistics of our Service.

#### HIPAA

Unlike a doctor or health plan, DocNetwork is not regulated by the Health Insurance Portability and Accountability Act (HIPAA), a federal law that establishes data confidentiality standards for patient health information. This is because DocNetwork does not store data on behalf of health care providers. Instead, our primary relationship is with the user. Under HIPAA, patients have a right to obtain a copy of their medical records. If they choose to use DocNetwork, we’ll help them store and manage their medical records online.

Although DocNetwork is not covered by HIPAA, we are committed to user privacy and have in place strict data security policies and measures, and ensure that users control access to their information. We let users know what information we collect when they use DocNetwork, how we use it, and how we keep it safe. Users choose who views or adds information to their profile, and they can revoke access at any time.

If you have any questions about how the DocNetwork data confidentiality practices compare to those mandated by HIPAA, you can view our [HIPAA](http://www.campdoc.com/hipaa) information.

#### Changing or Deleting Your Information

If you are a registered user, you may review, update or correct or the Personal Information provided in your registration or account profile. If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may update or delete it by making the change on your account settings. In some cases we may retain copies of your information if required by law.

#### Data Retention

We will retain your information for as long as your account is active or as needed to provide you services. If you wish to cancel your account or request that we no longer use your information to provide you services, you may delete your account. We may retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes, and enforce our agreements. Consistent with these requirements, we will try to delete your information quickly upon request. Please note, however, that there might be latency in deleting information from our servers and backed-up versions might exist after deletion.

#### Information Sharing and Disclosure

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information.

#### Security

The security of your information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information on our forms, we encrypt the transmission of that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL).

We follow generally accepted standards to protect the information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. If you have any questions about security on our website, you can view our Security Policy or contact us at security@docnetwork.org.

#### Changes to our Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy may change from time to time. If we make a change to this privacy policy that we believe materially reduces your rights, we will provide you with notice (for example, by email). And we may provide notice of changes in other circumstances as well. By continuing to use the Service after those changes become effective, you agree to be bound by the revised Privacy Policy.
